publy.net 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy – Publy

Publy takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy governs and details the main privacy principles we apply to the data we collect through our services.

### 1 -About Publy’s services

Publy specializes in creating personalized advertisements. We work with online partners to build advertisements for users who visit their website or mobile applications and with publishers to display personalized advertisements.

Our aim is to deliver advertisements by displaying products and/or personalized banners that you might be interested in, based on your recent browsing behavior. For example, if you visit and browse on Website/mobile application A, on a subsequent online visit to Website/mobile application B, you will see ads personalized by your browsing history on Website/mobile application A.

With our service, you should receive personalized ads that are more relevant for you than the standard advertising you would receive without Publy. [Click here for more information on Interest Based Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising).

In our adv tag could run some different ads from many agencies, for example:

 **Google AdSense** : <http://www.google.com/intl/en/ads>  
**OpenX** : <http://openx.com/legal/openx-website-privacy-principles/>  
**Criteo** : <http://www.criteo.com/privacy/>  
**Rubicon Project** : <http://rubiconproject.com/privacy/>  
**Xaxis** : <http://www.xaxis.com/static/view/privacy-policy>  
**AppNexus** : <http://www.appnexus.com/privacy-policy>  
**Zedo** : <http://www.zedo.com/about-zedo/privacy-policy/>  
**OutBrain** : <http://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy-713>  
**Google Analytics** : <https://www.google.it/intl/it/policies/>  
**nugg.ad** : <https://nugg.ad/en/privacy/general-information.html>

### 2 – Our technology

Online web environment: _(desktop, tablet, and smartphone browsers)_  
Publy “tags” visitors to its partners’ websites with browser cookies. Users tagged by Publy are given a technical identifier. At no point does Publy collect identifying personal data such as your name or address.  
The browser cookies track the products viewed by the visitor and pages visited of the partner for whom Publy is delivering ads. Pixel tags are used by Publy to transfer browsing data from visitors of our partner’s websites to Publy’s servers.

 **What are cookies?**  
A cookie is a small text file stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. There are two types of cookies:  
Session cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate on websites. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.  
Persistent cookies are used to run our technology as they enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our partners’ websites. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your internet browser’s ‘help’ file.

 **What are pixel tags?**  
A pixel tag _(also commonly known as a web beacon)_ is an industry-standard, often-transparent graphic image usually no larger than a 1×1 pixel that is placed in a website.  
Our partners’ advertisements are displayed on many websites, also known as “publishers.” These publishers may also place cookies on your browser. These cookies are there so that the publishers recognize that Publy has a personalized advertisement available for your browser.

 **Browser matching:** _(desktop, tablet, and smartphone browsers)_  
To serve you our personalized advertisements and provide a harmonized web experience we may match your identifiers on the different browsers you are using. At no point we collect identifying personal data such as your name or address to operate the matching.

We use exact matching methods by leveraging our advertising partner’s identifiers or email hash that they may pass to us. See data collection paragraph to learn more. Matching your devices only works in the online environement _(browser to browser)_ ; mobile application environment remains separate.

 **Other environments** _(Mobile applications)_  
In environments that do not support cookies, like mobile applications, we may use other similar technologies for the same purpose of cookies. To serve our ads in mobile applications we collect identifiers, such as Google Advertising ID or IDFA depending on the operating system of your mobile device. These identifiers consist in a string of technical and random characters singling out your device that Publy stored by Publy with a hash _(non reversible encrypting method)_.

### 3 – Data collection and use

We do not know who you are. We collect and use anonymous data relating to your browsing navigation to display personalized advertisements.  
We collect anonymous information  
We only collect data related to your browsing activity through cookies or equivalent identifiers that record:  
events related to your activity on the partner’s website _(such as the number of pages viewed, the products you viewed on that website, your searches made on the partner’s website)_ information related to your device _(device type, operating system, version)_ and events related to the Publy ad serving activity such as the number of ads displayed to you.  
We also collect technical user identifiers from our partners for the purpose of matching the browsers you use and serve you relevant ads based on your behaviour accross browsers.

 **For that purpose we process and store**

  1. We do not collect any identifying information
  2. We do not know who you are.
  3. We do not know your address, your place of work, your date of birth, your email address, your phone number.
  4. We do not use or store your IP address for targeting purposes*.
  5. We do not collect hardware-based identifiers such as UDID, Mac Address.
  6. We do not collect sensitive information _(such as religion, political opinion, health…)_.
  7. We collect this information in order to increase the relevancy of the ads being displayed to you.
  8. The data we collect is also used for reporting purposes, and to give our clients and partners more information about the performance of their advertising campaigns, and to improve performance over time.
  9. We do not create segments to specifically target children under 13 years old.
  10. We do not process any information which could be used by Publy, directly or indirectly, with the help of a third party or otherwise, to determine the personal identity of users.
  11. We share information collected with our subsidiaries or affiliated companies. We share aggregated data with our partners, i.e. data that does not permit identification of a partner, or permit you to be identified. We share non-aggregated data only upon approval of our partners and in compliance with our commercial agreements.
  12. We partner with Ad exchanges platforms to buy ad placements through auctions. Before the auction we match our ID with the ad exchange platform and then participate to the auction by sending the bid price and the banner code to display.

 *** In compliance with the best industry standards, we use IP addresses:**

  1.     1. For fraud detection purposes _(and not for targeting purposes)_ to help alert us to situations which could not have been caused by human behavior, such as a massive amount of clicking in a limited period of time;
    2. To extract geographical information.

### 4 – Your options to disable the display of Publy advertisements

Please note: that each environment is separate. If you do not want to receive Publy ads whatever device, browser used you must disable our services for both the online web and mobile app environments.

Online web environment: _(desktop, tablet, and smartphone browsers)_  
Please note: that this procedure will only block ads that are displayed by Publy. If you chose to opt out matched browsers, please note :  
that your opt-out on these matched browsers will be effective as soon as we see you again on these browsers if this happens within 6 weeks ;  
and that you may nonetheless continue to have cookies on other unmatched browsers and see ads displayed by Publy on these browsers.  
You can also opt out of Publy’s service by visiting the followings links.

Please note that these platforms allow you to opt out of interest-based advertising delivered by registered members on the current browser you are using.

### For EU:

IAB Europe opt-out platform (<http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>)  
You may also want to use browser settings to modify your preferences. At Publy our goal is to offer a harmonized online experience whatever browser you use. Most browsers accept our cookies by default but in certain cases, like Safari, our cookies are blocked by default by the browser settings _(and potentially without your knowledge)_. In these situations we will inform you before we drop our cookies so that you can tell us either that you want to experience our ads, or opt-out of our services by using the Publy opt-out. In cases where you interact with our service and want to experience our personalized ads your browser settings may nonetheless be configured to block certain third party cookies. In this situation, the most efficient way to disable our ads in for these browsers is by using our Opt-out.  
As described above, we elected to provide mechanisms of choice through our proprietary opt out and through industry platforms and do not respond to web browser do not track signals.

 **Other environments (Mobile applications)**  
Please note: to opt-out from advertising served by Publy in mobile applications, you must be browsing in applications.  
If you no longer want to be exposed to Publy personalized banners in the mobile application environment, you can opt out simply by clicking on the opt-out button accessible through the ad choices icons integrated in all our banners. (see complementary options for iOS and Android here under)  
Please note that this procedure will only block ads that are displayed by Publy. If you want to disable more services, please refer to your operating system settings, or follow instructions below. Your opt-out will be stored server side linked to your device ID.  
Android Users (version 2.3 and above)

To use the “opt-out of interest-based advertising” option, follow the instructions provided by Google here: [Google Play Help ](https://support.google.com/googleplay/answer/3405269).  
If you don’t have the Google Play Services installed on your device, you won’t receive Publy services.  
Please note that this is a device setting and will disable interest-based ads from all providers, and not just for Publy iOS users (version 6 and above)  
To use the “Limit Ad-Tracking” option, follow the instructions provided by Apple here: [Apple Support Center](https://www.apple.com/it/support/).  
Please note that this is a device setting and will disable interest-based ads from all providers, and not just for Publy  
Other Platforms  
Publy services only work with iOS _(version 6 and above)_ , so we do not provide interest-based ads on other platforms.

### 5 – Data security and retention

The security of your information is fundamental to Publy. We have implemented industry-standard security measures, which include the use of firewalls and encryption.  
We retain the technical data that we collect for up to 13 months from the date of collection. Our cookies expire 13 months after they are last updated.  
In the case of fraud detection, IP address may be retained for a maximum of 6 months for the purpose of investigating potentially fraudulent activity. The IP address is processed by teams separate to those responsible for the Publy algorithm.

### 6 – Denying / Revoking Consent

The user can deny / revoke consent to third party cookies by going to the third party links listed above or by visiting: https://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices

### 7 – Enabling / Disabling Cookies Through the Browser

Most browsers (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, etc.) are configured to accept Cookies. Cookies are stored on the hard drive of the user’s device and can be deleted. You can disable Cookies on the main website browsers by following the instructions provided at the following links:

 **Chrome**  
<https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=it>

**Firefox**  
<https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Eliminare%20i%20cookie>

**Internet Explorer**  
<https://windows.microsoft.com/it-it/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-10>

**Opera**  
<https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/>

**Safari**  
[https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US)

### 8 – Deleting Flash Cookies

By clicking the link below you can change the settings for Flash Cookies.  
Disabling Flash Cookies

### 9 – Contact

For any questions on this privacy policy, you can contact:  
**By email:** info@publy.net

Publy ltd  
22 Northumberland Road  
Ballsbridge, Dublin 4  
Ireland

### 10 – Changes to our privacy policy

Please note that we may update or change this privacy policy. If we revise our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and to other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any we disclose it. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective.

### Cookies

In order to provide a smoother and more intuitive navigation, the Site and Platform make use of Cookie Technology. Cookies are small text extensions stored by the browser on the User’s device with the intent of speeding up the process of analyzing internet traffic, thus improving the User’s access to the services provided by the Site. Cookies may contain information related to the User, collected and archived by the same User’s browser during navigation, some examples of which include the User’s preferences, tastes, interests, etc.

The eventual use of data collected by the Cookies generated by Publy is for the means of providing the client the best experience possible on the Site, as well as to identify the User and register their preferences for purposes strictly related to the provision of activities and/or service requested by the user. Third party Cookies may be present on certain pages of the Site, for the intent of tracking the functionality of services provided or to personalize said services based on the tastes and preferences of the User. Publy will not have access to said Cookies, nor will it have control over them.

The User may at any time deactivate and /or block the Cookies present in the browser by deactivating and blocking Cookie use through the browser or directly on the User’s device. Deactivating and/or blocking the transmission of Cookies may result in a reduction in the functionality of certain services or limited access to certain areas of the Site. For further information regarding the use of Cookies, please refer to the Cookie Policy present on the Site.
